app-mobile.net 2013-06-10

# Privacy | Free Android Apps

This blog does not share personal information with third parties nor do we store any information about your visit to this blog other than to analyze and optimize your content and reading experience through the use of cookies.

At [App-](http://www.app-mobile.net/category/android-app "app")Mobile.Net, the privacy of our visitors is extremely important. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected and how it is used.

This Privacy Policy is reviewed and revised from time to time. You will want to revisit it regularly. Your use of this site, in any and all forms, constitutes an acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

**1\. Log Files**

We use log files like many other websites. The information in the log files include:

  * Internet Protocol addresses (IP)
  * Types of browser
  * Internet Service Provider (ISP)
  * Date and time stamp
  * Referring and exit pages

All of this information is not linked to anything that is personally identifiable.

**2\. Cookies**

We use cookies to store information about visitor preferences and to record user-specific information on visits and pages the user views so as to provide a custom experience. In regard to third-party advertisers, We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit[http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.app-mobile.net/wp-content/plugins/htr-checkvirus/check.php?www.networkadvertising.org%2Fmanaging%2Fopt_out.asp).

If you wish to disable cookies you may do so through your web browser options. Instructions for doing so and for other cookie-related management can be found on the specific web browsers’ websites.

_DoubleClick DART Cookie_

Google, a third party vendor, uses the DART cookie to serve ads on App-Mobile.Net. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting [Google’s Content Network Privacy Policy](http://www.app-mobile.net/wp-content/plugins/htr-checkvirus/check.php?www.google.com%2Fprivacy%2Fads%2F).

**3\. Other**

Users might be asked to subscribe to our newsletter by providing name and email address to receive communication from App-Mobile.Net. We use a secure op-in subscription system and we reserve the right to contact subscribers with information related to this website and blog. Subscribers may unsubscribe anytime and every email delivered will contain an “Unsubscribe” link.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](http://www.app-mobile.net/contact-us) .
